Adhi Muhammad Fahmi

https://adhimf.my.id https://www.linkedin.com/in/adhi-muhammad-fahmi-571317213/ adhimfahmi@gmail.com +6281385476627 Bogor, Indonesia

EXPERIENCES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN PT. DYCODEX TEKNOLOGI NUSANTARA

September 2022 - January 2023

- Design and Develop Database Architecture of De-Lansia Monitoring System with PostgreSQL (PSQL), Supabase, and Platformatic.js.
- Design UI Design of De-Lansia Android App with Figma.
- Develop and Implemented Mockup Design to Android App with Flutter (Dart).
- Do Quality Check of Connectivity and Realtime between De-Lansia Wearable Device and De-Lansia Monitoring Android App.
- Develop Landing Page of **De-Lansia Website** with Next.js and Vercel (Hosting Server).

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

BASIC COMPUTING LABORATORY TELKOM UNIVERSITY

July 2021 - July 2022

- Develop and Maintenance daskomlab.com.
- Fix Bug Issues of Front-End and Back-End Features.
- Maintenance practicum and recruitment databases (MySQL, SQL, PhpMyAdmin).
- Develop New Features of Practicum Web Apps.
- **Mentor** of the next batch Basic Computing Laboratory Software Developer.
- Manage and Maintenance VPS of daskomlab.com (Bash and Linux).

PRACTICUM ASSISTANT

BASIC COMPUTING LABORATORY TELKOM UNIVERSITY

August 2020 - July 2022

- Teach Algorithm and Basic Programming for practicum with C language.
- Coordinator of Assignment and Task Committee who to organize team to create, develop, and review all of assignment and task of practicum materials.

PROJECTS

SEMI-AUTOMATION COFFEE ROASTER | COMMUNITY SERVICE

June 2022 - August 2022

Semi-Automation Coffee Roaster is system to help and facilitate UMKM at Haruman, Cimaung, Bandung Regency to roasting Arabica Coffee. **Youtube Video** and **View Repository**.

GRAB IT FAST 2021 TELKOM UNIVERSITY EVENT WEBSITE

March 2021 - June 2021

Major As Front-End Dev. and Implemented Design with customize bootstrap from Designer Team. **View Repository**.

DASKOMLAB RECRUITMENT WEBSITE

February 2021 - June 2021

A recruitment website of new batch Daskom Laboratory Assistants. Which has a variety of features such as: Admin feature, Logistic feature, Assistant Candidates feature, Stage Announcements, and Select a stage schedule of recruitment. **View Repository**.

SUMMARY

Final year student of Bachelor Degree Electrical Engineering, Telkom University and active as A Full-Stack Web and Mobile Developer for Web Development with massive passion and adaptive communication to collaborate with a team to reach team goals. Also Have done some research with lecturers about IoT, automation systems, and embedded systems research during bachelor's degree study. And now planned to be graduated on August 2023 as Bachelor Electrical Engineering.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING TELKOM UNIVERSITY

Expected August 2023, Bandung GPA: 3.92

SKILLS

PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS,
TailwindCSS, Laravel, Vue.js, Next.js,
Flutter (Dart), SQL, PostgreSQL, MySQL,
Platformatic.js, Python, C, Bash, Git,
Linux, Figma (UX/UI Design),
Supabase, Nginx, Adaptive, Research,
Communication, Flexible, Teamwork,
Time Management, Problem-Solving,
Decision-Making, Leadership.

CONTACTS

Github: adhiiimf

LinkedIn: Adhi Muhammad Fahmi

Instagram: adhiiimf

PORTFOLIO

• Daskom Web Apps: daskomlab.com

• De-Lansia Android Apps: Playstore

• Daskom Recruitment Web: **Repo**

• TOP 100 Innovillage 2019: Portfolio